<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Organization on dwblab - Home of Douglas Breault: Innovative Leadership and Engineering</title>
    <link>https://www.dwblab.com/categories/organization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Organization on dwblab - Home of Douglas Breault: Innovative Leadership and Engineering</description>
    <image>
      <title>dwblab - Home of Douglas Breault: Innovative Leadership and Engineering</title>
      <url>https://www.dwblab.com/douglas-breault-headshot.jpg</url>
      <link>https://www.dwblab.com/douglas-breault-headshot.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.dwblab.com/categories/organization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Return to Office Announcements: Why Your Best People Are So Upset</title>
      <link>https://www.dwblab.com/posts/return-to-office-announcements-why-your-best-people-are-upset/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dwblab.com/posts/return-to-office-announcements-why-your-best-people-are-upset/</guid>
      <description>The COVID-19 pandemic sent shockwaves across the globe, forcing many organizations to shift from office-first to remote work almost overnight. Tech companies, in particular, seemed well-positioned to adapt to this change. Companies continued to grow and launch new products. However, as the world recovers and offices start to reopen, a number of high-profile tech companies are choosing to return to the office. While a number of reasons are cited for this shift back to the office a common thread seems to be a belief that these company&amp;#39;s problems are best solved by increasing physical proximity. They seem to argue that the challenges experienced during remote work are unique to the remote environment and are best addressed by getting back to the office. But is this really the case? Why are so many people upset about these return to office announcements?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
