<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>decision-making on dwblab - Home of Douglas Breault: Innovative Leadership and Engineering</title>
    <link>http://www.dwblab.com/tags/decision-making/</link>
    <description>Recent content in decision-making on dwblab - Home of Douglas Breault: Innovative Leadership and Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.dwblab.com/tags/decision-making/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the Quality of Decisions in Hindsight: A Comprehensive Guide for Leaders</title>
      <link>http://www.dwblab.com/blog/evaluating-decision-quality-comprehensive-guide-for-engineering-leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dwblab.com/blog/evaluating-decision-quality-comprehensive-guide-for-engineering-leaders/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:
Brief recap of the previous blog post. Introduction to the new topic: evaluating decision quality in hindsight. The importance of this topic for leaders and teams. The Illusion of Resulting:
Explanation of the concept: judging decisions based on outcomes. Examples of the illusion of resulting in various contexts. Why this approach is flawed and can lead to incorrect evaluations of decision quality. Result-Independent Decision Evaluation:
The importance of evaluating decisions independently of the outcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlock Organizational Transformation with Consent-Based Decision-Making</title>
      <link>http://www.dwblab.com/blog/unlock-organizational-transformation-consent-decision-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.dwblab.com/blog/unlock-organizational-transformation-consent-decision-making/</guid>
      <description>Decisions: they are fundamental to any organization. They shape strategy, influence culture, and define our daily work. But who gets to make these decisions, and how? That&amp;rsquo;s a question that&amp;rsquo;s been the subject of much debate and experimentation, and the answer can have a profound impact on the success and culture of an organization.
All too often I&amp;rsquo;ve seen teams making incredibly important decisions with no thought into how they come to the decision.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
